Dev Bhanushali

Projects & Portfolios

- https://devb.vercel.app/
- https://github.com/dev-9820/

Summary

Recent graduate with education and internship experience in web development. Highly poised and dedicated with talent in design principles and programming languages. Excellent eye for visual aesthetics paired with insight into data and backend functionality.

Skills

- React & Next JS
- Node & Express JS
- AngularJS
- PHP (Flask / Django)
- API Building

- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Python
- C# / C++
- Kubernetes

- Data Visualization
- Game Development
- VR App Development
- · Digital Animation

Experience

FULL STACK DEVELOPER 10/2024 - Current

Qriocity, Mumbai, India

Created back-end services for data manipulation and business logic using Node.js and Express.

Developed and maintained front-end web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and ReactJS.

Collaborated with other developers in designing solutions for customer requirements.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERN 05/2024 - 08/2024

Ierix Infotech, Mumbai, India

Developed, tested, and deployed new features on the website using the MERN Stack.

Built CRM components for database and client management using PHP.

Built an E-commerce Website from Scratch for a Partner Company.

Debugged existing codebases and identified solutions for improvement, and suggested for better efficiency that turned out to save 12% cost to the company.

WEB DEVELOPER AND ANIMATION INTERN 06/2023 - 09/2023

PrismTech, Mumbai, India

Developed **visually engaging 3D animations** showcasing the manufacturing processes of the company. Upgraded the company's website with 3D Models using **3D JavaScript Libraries**.

Rendered 3D models using Blender 3D Animation Software.

Supported such 3D Renders for Client Presentations.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science And Electronics, 05/2024 **Shah & Anchor Engineering College**, Mumbai

High School Diploma, 04/2020 **K.J. Somaiya College of Science & Commerce**, Mumbai